What happened last night with Sven?
I was hoping you'd allow me to introduce you to our Managing Director.
Kaz, why did you ask me to come here?
You might knock some sense into her.
I need a six course, executive luncheon, for less than a tenner a head.
No problem.
Come on, then!
Let's see if your bottle's as big as your gob.
My wife underestimates.
She has no idea of the things I notice.
Footage from the day me dad died.
'Can I see you tomorrow?'
Mum?
Hey, guys, who wants some chow?
Do you actually know what that means?
Er, hello?
Fodder?
Nosebag?
Nosh?
What?
You might wanna choose your words more carefully.
Unless you're actually offering oral sex?
Hey, if everyone else is up for it!
Oh, God.
Oh, I forgot, I'm a parent.
What's up, Dougie?
You sitting down?
Yeah.
Just had a call from Vinny Haslam.
That executive dinner?
Next week, 20 people.
Pull it off and I get the contract, yeah?
He wants to bring it forward...to five o'clock today.
It's a wind-up.
Piss-take.
It's like, totally MI, right?
Mission Impossible.
Obviously.
Which is obviously the point.
Venue unseen?
Up against the clock?
Can she deliver?
Nita...
Guys, how would you like to earn a shed-load of bees?
Nothing you could offer me would make it worth my while.
20 squids and I get Magda to muck out your room?
30 and she does my biology coursework?
Deal.
Arlo?
What can I offer you?
I'm sure I can think of something.
You're doing it?
Creepster!
35, bottle of Baileys AND an Atticus beanie.
Now we're talking.
You couldn't afford me.
Right.
Who's next?
Whatever you're selling we don't want it.
40 quid, crate of Boddies, and two days off in lieu?
Unbelievable!
Bit of keg, a few shraps and she thinks she can hijack my day of rest?
That'll be a yes, then.
Dennis...can't...sell up.
Someone needs to talk him out of it.
Someone?
Or me?
Why do you think I'm still here?
The X Factor?
What's he on about?
It's the eyesight's gone pluto, Beth not the ears or the nouse.
Right.
I'll leave you ladies to it.
He knows.
What?
More than he lets on.
And he's right about you and Nash.
You owe him some explanations.
Do I?
Mmm.
Why you left.
Yeah, like I'm really gonna tell him.
Not all of it, obviously.
But isn't it time he knew it wasn't just about him?
What's she offer you?
30 quid, a tomato plant and eternal gratitude.
Hiya.
Notice she didn't ask you.
I couldn't, anyway.
I'm on a mission, remember?
Oh, yeah.
Just the one?
Oh!
I thought you'd be someone else.
Who?
A potential buyer, actually.
Oh, really.
Why d'you think I've never had a boyfriend?
Can't imagine.
Do you think it's weird?
Er, no.
Not in your case.
I suppose I've never been that fussed about lads.
Mmm.
Could never really see myself getting involved.
But now I think, yeah, why not?
BETH SIGHS Yeah...
If it was the right person.
He don't exist, Al.
I think he might.
Oh, dream on.
Oh, I do.
All the time.
Mmm.
All kinds of dreams.
Yeah, you don't say!
Dreams are important.
Bryce says we should always pay attention to dreams.
The one this morning, well, I think it was important.
Well, Bryce says everything's important.
He says we should always look for the hidden agenda.
So in the dream, it's like I was her, I was Mum, collecting the letter I wrote, asking her to come home.
Where?
Marrakech, I suppose.
That's where I sent it, that post restauranty place Phil gave me.
I think I should tell Bryce.
Mmm.
He said to let him know if there's any developments, any progress with me.
How likely is that?
..
Let me in, for Christ's sake!
She's pecking me head in.
I were just telling her about this dream I had.
Finally, 6.45, clear course six, and serve coffee, liqueurs and petit fours.
Any questions?
When did you first realise you'd lost the plot?
Next?
When do the others get here?
Which?
The ten extra pair of hands we'll need if we've any chance of delivering what you just described.
That's the difference between us, Beth.
You see a problem, I see a challenge.
No, the difference is I have a conscience, you take the piss.
You expect people to do you a favour on shit wages.
Me, I wouldn't even ask.
Which is why I have a turnover of half a million a year, and you're still frying bacon.
.. OK, guys, pinnies on.
Wow!
She's hard-core, your mum.
Don't even think about being impressed.
Building bridges.
Making amends.
All so easy, 20 years too late.
I just thought if we could go out for a drink, just you and me.
I don't do out.
Since when?
Since you nobbed off, and I stayed in to mind Head the Ball.
Dennis, I know what that must've been like.
Do you?
Every day?
Watching him shrivel, pining for the Marrakech trollop.
Letters that never arrived, kids that never visited, grandkids he's never even seen!
He deserved better.
OK?
YOU deserved better.
Like you give a shit.
I do, actually.
I wasn't happy, leaving you to deal with him, but at the time it seemed...
What did it seem?
Like the only option.
Do you ever hear from her?
Do you know what?
No.
Apparently it's only you she keeps in touch with.
Just the odd postcard.
Well, aren't you the favoured one?
As far as we were concerned, she might as well not exist.
Valium.
You need this?
No, not remotely!
20 years caring for Alco-Pop.
Sat in here so long, I can't even step out my own front door for more than half an hour, and even then I need a gang of bow-wows as armed escort.
No, course I don't need it!
Anyhow, since you're here, I expect you'd like to hear what some of the prospective buyers have talked about doing to the place.
Diced, guys, not bludgeoned to a pulp.
How do you fancy two tickets for Michael Buble and a bottle of Asti?
One guy was talking about knocking through the whole ground floor, doing the open-plan thing.
And then pushing down into the cellars and making a new basement flat.
Wow.
Who'd want to live down here?
It's so poky and dark.
Well, at the moment, yeah.
They'd need to excavate, obviously.
What?
You know, lower the floor.
They'd need more height.
SHE SIGHS Dennis.
Yeah?
Are you sure about this?
It's been your home for 40 years.
You'd be mad to sell if you're so attached.
I'm not.
Why would I be?
This place reminds me of everything I detest.
Secrets, dishonesty, denial.
Denial?
Er, these, for instance.
This.
You don't think it's weird that not one person has asked me why.
Well, maybe...
Not one person!
OK, then.
Why?
Our dear departed mother.
Metaphorically speaking.
After she bailed out, me and Dad were going through some of her stuff - scent, nail varnish, make-up.
I put some on.
Make him laugh, I thought.
He didn't laugh.
He freaked out.
Well, that was it.
I kept going back to it and going back and when it was used up I bought some more.
But Dad, he was such a bigot.
Cope?
He didn't.
He went feral every time.
Why do you think I did it?
To wind him up.
So it was just...?
So you're not actually...?
Tranny Two Shoes?
Might be.
Might not.
Who wants to know?
Answer?
No-one.
No-one dares.
"Deviant in the room, let's pretend it's not happening."
Well, it is happening.
It's all happening, Phil, and you'd better wake up to the idea.
Including the fact that I am most definitely selling up.
So I suggest you go away and decide what you wanna do next.
Can you believe this?
House full of people who'd sooner be out getting wankered or still in bed?
Instead of which they're all here, doing what she wants.
How do they fall for it every time?
Cos she knows just how to reel them in.
She gives it the face.
The big eyes, soft voice, the guilt trip, the bribe.
HORN TOOTS Not to mention the 'string 'em along in the hope of a shag'.
(Hiya. )
'So guess where I am.'
Inside or out?
Out.
The tree.
How's the artwork?
Well, I'm guessing your carpentry skills are a bit more... refined these days.
What a loser!
So when can I see you?
Soon as.
Where?
West Dene.
You're kidding!
KNOCK ON DOOR Anybody home?
Coming, Dougie.
Look, you know where to look.
I've gotta go.
Just get there.
Wait for me.
Dougie, don't look so worried!
I just hope you know what you're taking on.
Thought I'd drop by, check it's all under control.
You know Nita.
Military precision in all things.
Right, I'm short of waiters.
Do you fancy pitching in?
Er...
I would, but I'm one of the guests.
Vinny's asked me to escort his niece.
And this niece is how old?
About 22.
But can I just say I think you should be turning your thoughts to the venue.
He's not thinking of pairing you off with her?
I'm not sure what exactly you're expecting.
We both know you'd be better off with someone more mature.
I think it might present something of a challenge.
Not a looker, and not a smart-arse - you don't want her giving you the run-around.
What sort of a challenge?
Let's just say it's lucky that your husband's a master carpenter.
I need a favour.
Please?
Pretty please?
Well, far be it from me to state the obvious.
I know, but it's what Haslam wants.
It's his new baby, he wants to show it off.
I did warn Nita it wouldn't be straightforward.
Can you build me a frame so we can light the table from above?
And Dougie, you've OK'd it so we can use the on-site kitchen?
Cool.
So we'll need the chairs and the fold-up table we used for the staff Christmas dinner.
Plus our table linen, cutlery, glassware.
Nita, I really don't think you need to go this far.
Oh, you don't?
So I needn't push the boat out and lay on a really spectacular show?
I shouldn't aim to have the contract in the bag by the end of the meal?
Yes, but Nita, in two hours?
I'll get my tools.
Did I tell you the weird thing that happened yesterday in my session with Bryce?
Please tell me he hypnotised himself into a coma?
Don't encourage her.
You'll never hear the last of it.
Aren't you glad she's getting some help?
No!
I prefer her screwed up and quiet.
SHE MOUTHS Do you fancy him?
No.
Think about him all the time?
Imagine him tongue-wrestling you?
No!
What you doing?
Phoning him.
Lola!
Well, find out what his game is, what his intentions are.
No, don't!
Give me the phone.
Oh, it's ringing!
'Bryce Waghorn?'
Yes.
I'm calling about Alice Tyler.
Yeah?
What about her?
Well, I understand you've been subjecting her to some rather unusual practices.
What do you mean?
Well, some very unorthodox methods.
Who is this?
Look, I don't know what she's been telling you, but...
Well, whatever you've done, it's worked.
Cos, er, she's got the hots for you.
Don't!
Give me the phone.
Ah, sweet!
She's blushing!
God, I am so sorry.
That was my niece, just ignore her.
I have never at any point...
Alice, it's OK.
What she's saying is not exactly news to me.
What d'you mean?
It's a well-known phenomenon.
Clients having strong feelings for their therapists.
It's called transference.
No, but...
It's by no means a bad thing if it facilitates the process.
It engenders a greater sense of trust.
So...lots of people feel like this?
I'm...
I'm not sort of weird?
No, no, not at all.
Refreshingly normal.
In fact, so normal, I doubt you'll be needing to see me much longer.
But I want to.
I need to.
You're the only person who doesn't take the piss.
Well, you can.
When?
Soon?
I've got a pretty full schedule but I might just be able to carve out an hour this afternoon.
SHE SIGHS I can't, I'm working.
Best leave it, then.
No!
No, I'll see what I can manage.
I'll get a taxi or something.
I've gotta go.
OK, I've thought.
I'd like to make an offer on the place myself.
Listen up!
Whatever stage we're at, I want you to finish off, pack up and move across to the venue.
We've got less than two hours to complete food prep, plate up, and create a dining room out of a building site.
Peasy.
You'll need your smart clothes, aprons...
Sense of humour.
And the ability to clamp your beak when you feel a moan coming on.
And I still need three more waiters, so any sensible suggestions, let me know.
OK, let's move.
Nice way to spend a Sunday.
Girls, come on, it's for us, not just me.
We deliver the goods, we get the contract.
We get the contract, we're all in the mint.
Except some of us are more minted than others.
OK, guys, food in here.
Cutlery, crockery, glassware, follow me.
Hello?
Hero worship?
Isn't this guy just a total star?
How can I ever repay you?
By never again reneging on our agreement to keep our businesses totally separate.
Dougie, can you organise the seating?
Ethan, Lola, give him a hand.
Arlo, come with me.
You're well fit, you know that?
Let's just pretend you didn't say that and I didn't hear it.
Say the word and I'll give Lola the push.
Why would you do that?
I think we have a future.
You and me.
Sweetheart, I think we need to talk.
Dennis, now is not a good moment.
Well, that's cool, cos it's not great news.
I've had another offer for the house.
How?
Surely no-one else knows you're selling?
Who's it from?
Oh, you surely wouldn't want me breaking client confidentiality by giving you a name?
'Course, you could always up your bid.
'I know you wouldn't want me being short-changed.'
Specially if we've both misread the market.
Dennis, can I get back to you?
Obviously I want to make sure you're getting a fair price.
It's just now's not a good time.
Oh!
Did I mention how much interest there's been?
Oh, I don't mean recently.
Since before Dad died.
You didn't, no.
Whole rake of enquiries.
Well, I say "enquiries".
At first we thought it was pranksters.
Threats, incentives, you name it, they just kept coming.
In fact, we began to wonder if there wasn't a bigger picture.
That's when we started recording the calls.
Really?
And?
Interesting.
Could I listen?
Why not?
WOMAN ON 'You do realise this area's going to be bulldozed to make way for a new motorway?
'If I were you I'd sell up now, while you can still get a decent price.'
Any more?
Oh, sure, if you're interested.
'Listen, pal, I can only protect you for so long.
'My superior's not a patient man, and when he wants something...'
That's a bit scary.
Any more?
'Hello, I'm doing a survey for the Eccles and Patricroft Bugle.
I'm wondering what you, as a resident of Elgin Park, think of the recent crime wave in your area?
'You what?
Can you say you feel safe in your home these days with feral gangs roaming the streets?'
That's the form these days, is it?
You see a place you like, you put the bite on the owners?
No, it's really not.
It's weird, though.
Sudden mad spurt of interest, all these people desperate to buy.
Yeah.
Unless it's the same person.
Oh, c'mon!
Who would seriously sink so low?
Don't let me keep you!
I won't.
You don't seem too curious about these calls.
It's water under the bridge.
No, but what's weird, that last one, the thing about feral gangs...
Yeah?
Well, the night Dad died, there was a gang, wasn't there?
Yeah, but...
A gang, Dennis.
Was it coincidence?
Well, what else would it be?
Had you ever seen them before?
No.
Would you recognise them again?
Not that I haven't tried.
Played back the tape enough times.
Tape?
Security cam footage from the night it happened.
You still have it?
Somewhere.
Could I see it?
Could be anyone.
This is it.
This is what did it for Dad.
This is what brought on his heart attack.
But as you can see, it's all so blurred, totally unrecognisable.
So... there's not much point in pursuing it any further.
Is there?
I don't know.
I need to think.
You think there might be something we should follow up?
I don't know.
I need to think.
These girls.
They think they know it all.
But they haven't got a clue.
How come you never told me you were outside Dad's house the night he died?
Chill, guys.
Take a breath.
Can't talk.
It's Armageddon Central here.
I'll call you later.
Shit.
'Hi, it's Beth, you know what to do.'
Beth, call me back.
Now!
45 minutes.
Beth, Alice, start laying out the appetisers.
Lois, you're in charge of salads.
Nancy, you're garnishings.
Ethan, you're washing up.
Right.
Did anyone come up with any waiters?
Er...
20 squids and a case of Stella apiece?
You are joking!
I said desperate, not a death wish!
I'm silver-service trained.
Used to wait on at Talk Of The North.
We'll point him in the right direction!
Coolio!
OK!
Come in, grab a pinny.
Anyone ever served wine?
Down his neck at the rate of four kegs a night!
OK, so these are your roles for the rest of the afternoon.
Please listen, it gets boring when I have to repeat myself.
Right, switches.
These are your lights, this is your audio here.
You're going?
Yeah.
Sure you won't need it.
You know, it's time's like this a girl really needs someone to hold her hand.
Nita, I have never met anyone less in need of hand-holding.
Whereas me, I'm in need of a beer.
You could have one here.
I really don't wanna be here.
It's my Sunday.
Where are you going?
What's with the inquisition?
I know where you're going.
I can absolutely guarantee you don't.
Nash, wait.
Nita?
Don't go.
I think you're wanted.
I've just had a call from Sven.
They're on their way.
But they're half an hour early!
Of course they are!
That's the point, right?
OK.
We can do this.
Is that your court appearance outfit?
I can manage!
Oh, yeah, since when?
I'm not getting shown up by you looking like a toerag!
'Eagle Cars.'
Hello?
'Yes, love.'
Can I book a cab, please?
You kept our flat.
Wow, look at that.
Wow.
She's really gone to town.
Full marks for presentation.
Looks like someone might have to eat their words.
Mr and Mrs Haslam, Mr Carlsson.
Er...
We're early.
We're ready!
Please, sit down.
Here we go.
Thank you.
Guys, I love you!
You all know what you're doing.
Hopefully.
I don't need to say how critical it is that this goes off without a hitch.
Kaz, you're absolutely sure?
You say that again and I'll do you for discrimination!
Fine!
Let's do it, guys.
And the game yesterday.
You saw United at Liverpool?
Mm.
Game was fine.
Could've done without the side-show though.
We had this appalling yob behind us.
One of the old '80s brigade.
Archaic ideas, mouth like a sewer.
Vinny soon sorted it.
You had him ejected?
Her.
It was a woman.
No offence.
But I feel safer with you behind the scenes.
Hiya.
I'm trying to book a cab.
This way, guys!
Cheers.
At least it's, er, decent wine.
I'd like to tell you a bit about each dish before we serve.
We're starting with a little amuse-bouche.
Parmesan tuilles with a green pea and mint sorbet and a ginger and celeriac coulis.
Ginger what?
Thank you.
Just look at the way this is arranged!
Marvellous.
Let's try it.
Have you had this before?
Doesn't it look delicious.
So what do you do here?
Well, I play old songs, look at old photos.
Stick pins in effigies of Dan.
It's an investment.
It's an office cum kid-free Nita free zone.
How often d'you use it?
Less than you'd think.
Actually I own the whole house.
I own lots of houses.
But Nita thinks...
She think I'm just a carpenter.
Which of course officially I am.
But I've got a very healthy sideline.
About which she knows nothing.
Because if she did...
She'd wanna get involved!
And I don't much care for the way she does business, so I keep it under wraps.
Wise man.
And this is just small-talk.
I know.
That's OK.
I've got all day.
What about you?
CROCKERY CLATTERS Oh, sorry about that.
You still here?
Don't I get time off for good behaviour?
When I see some, I'll let you know!
Look, I really need something in the next half hour.
Ethan?
All right?
I'll pop this on there.
Whoa!
Hey!
What the hell d'you think you're doing?!
It's cool!
We'll do this another time, yeah!
I can't get a cab.
No problem.
I'll come and collect you.
JJ, Georgie, Ethan, Arlo.
Collect the plates.
Remember, clearing from the right.
Right.
Ethan, move!
Move!
Two minutes, guys.
Right, got it.
Need some cutlery.
What you doing?
I'm seeing Bryce, OK?
I've got an emergency session booked.
Oh, please(!)
I'll be half an hour.
Are you off your head?
Nita'll go baboon!
Well, it's tough shit.
Alice!
I am sick of putting other people first.
This is MY Sunday.
It's MY appointment.
Nita can swivel.
Look, if it's a bad time we can easily postpone.
No, no!
I really feel like I'm getting somewhere.
Like I'm on the verge of something.
Another breakthrough?
Yeah!
Then we should definitely go for it.
So.
Are we ready to do some work?
Deffo!
Happy in your work, Dad?
He doesn't get out much!
I could be looking at a new career!
Any plans for the summer?
What is she wearing?
She just doesn't get it right.
For the second course, we have herbed filo purses filled with Brie and gravad lax, with a Meaux mustard and tarragon salsa.
That's lovely, absolutely delicious.
That's haute cuisine?
Have you seen the flower?
Looks like a small pasty.
It's just beautiful.
An edible work of art.
Where's Alice?
I thought I told you to stay in the kitchen.
Where is she?
Going deeper.
Going deeper than you've ever gone before.
All your limbs are becoming heavy, incredibly heavy, becoming so heavy you couldn't move even the slightest muscle.
And yet, you're going deeper.
And just when you think you can't go any deeper, you will step down to another level, another depth.
And there, at that deepest level where you've never gone before, you'll find me waiting for you.
WOMAN'S Help!
So obviously there are things you wanna ask me.
Such as?
What I've been doing all these years?
Not really.
About Dan?
Nope.
Why I left?
Seemed clear enough.
You got a job offer.
We'd hit a rocky patch.
We might have come through it.
You seemed to be in a hurry to leave.
I assumed you had your reasons.
Oh, I did have my reasons.
You wanna give me a clue?
Don't!
Dad!
Stop it!
What have you done?
Dad?
SHE SCREAMS Stop!
Wait!
Please!
Let me explain!
Can I?
Will you let me?
Bastard!
No!
Hear me out!
I'm begging you, let's be calm about this.
You bastard!
OK.
Number one.
This was a major breakthrough.
What?
Warrior work!
I mean I would never have dreamed of letting it go this far, only you asked me.
What?
You don't remember?
That's interesting.
What did I ask you?
We went deep.
While you were in the Regressed Hypnotic State, you told me that you had intimacy issues you were desperate to overcome.
Oh, come on!
You begged me to help you work through your inhibitions!
What, by shagging me!
Please don't use that word!
I prefer to call it "Primary Intimate Congress".
And it's what you wanted!
I thought you were ready.
If it's too soon, if you've lost faith in yourself, in the process.
I haven't.
Well, that's excellent.
I have lost faith in you.
Alice, wait!
Alice!
There's something you need to know.
What you're experiencing is perfectly normal!
What?
Shock?
Disgust?
It's absolutely part of the process.
And the next step.
D'you want me to tell you?
You're unbelievable!
It'll come when you discover that beneath all this anger and outrage, and self-loathing even, is the realisation of what we've been working towards!
That's right.
Hey.
See, somewhere in there you already know.
Can you hear it?
And what is it saying to you?
Set me free.
Let me tell you my name.
It's desire, Alice.
OK, so one day you're here, the next you're gone.
No explanations, no calls.
Maybe I thought you'd follow me.
Maybe I thought I'd follow you.
Why didn't you?
Why didn't you invite me?
Did you need inviting?
Yes.
Always?
Oh, here we go.
If I'd wanted to eat lettuce I'd move into a hutch!
Is there any chance of a bacon bap?
He's joking!
Oh no, he's not!
Arugula, pear and asiago salad with mango-infused olive oil and zucchini and red chilli garnish.
I'd've been happy with scotch eggs and lemon meringue pie!
You've no clue about haute cuisine!
Nita, sweetheart, it's fabulous!
Perhaps you should come and join us.
Yeah, let the staff do their own bit for a change.
Oh, I couldn't possibly.
I like to oversee everything in person.
Bad news.
Sorry?
If you can't trust your staff, why employ them?
Well...
Do you want to know the secret of my success?
Ask Sven.
What do I look for in all my associates?
Can they delegate?
Secure in the knowledge that they've made good choices, got the right people.
That whatever happens out of sight, behind their back, everything'll turn out fine.
Have you thought of me, over the years?
Every single day.
Next?
I've thought of you.
I'm flattered.
Next?
I hated you for not coming after me.
I made myself not come.
I made myself stay away.
I married Nita to get at you.
I know you did!
What were we like?
Crazy.
Intense.
Couldn't leave each other alone.
Still can't.
Phil, what do you want?
You could've come to the church and left after the funeral.
Why are you still here?
To bury this once and for all.
How?
OK, what if, just say, we've built up this whole thing?
Each other, our three years together, into this amazing myth?
What if the reality was much less dramatic?
Is much less?
Isn't worth wrecking lives for?
What if we went ahead and trashed our families, blew our lives apart.
And six months down the line we realised there was nothing to it, and all we needed was to get each other out of our systems?
How?
Just once.
And then... we put the relationship...
To bed.
And move on.
OK.
Just once, then...
Just once.
It's a pleasure to experience a more refined cuisine.
At least some of us appreciate it.
Personally, I think it raises us above the level of the brute beasts.
What?
The ability to digest rabbit food?
Perhaps we should have given some to our little friend from yesterday!
Ahem.
You don't recognise me?
Sorry?
Or my husband?
Should I?
From the match yesterday?
You treated us to an outburst of your filth!
And she calls me a liability.
Did I?
You don't remember?
Nothing personal.
I do it all the time.
Get carried away.
That's bloody rich!
My wife was appalled.
She's never heard such language like it in her life.
Doesn't go to many games?
Beth.
Comes with the territory, expect verbal!
They're United, not PC City!
Mr Haslam, I really had no idea.
I have serious doubts about your judgment if this is the kind of person you employ.
What does it matter what she does on her day off?
Alice.
She's allowed to sound off if she wants!
Alice!
She said it weren't personal.
You know, it probably was.
Were you the knob-head calling Fletcher a spas?
You don't slag your own team.
Alice, stop!
Beth, just take the plates and go.
I think Beth had every right.
Hey, and take this tripe with you!
Hey, that's way offside!
There's a lot of effort gone into that food.
Has it?!
Well, I'll tell you what, Sonny Jim, here's what I think it's fit for!
And you know what?
Here's what I think you're fit for!
You little...
Hey, hey!
Dennis?
I can't talk now.
Well, I think you'd better cos it's high time we sacked the bullshit!
Where were you the night Dad died?
What?
How is this relevant?
See, I think he'd be on the warpath if he knew what you'd been up to.
Course, maybe he does know.
Maybe he is on the warpath.
I can't talk now, I'm really tied...
Make it go!
Get it away!
Over there!
What?
There!
Who was it?
An intruder?
We should call security.
There's no point, it wasn't an intruder.
Someone you recognise?
Someone you know?
Yes!
My father.
Your late father?
Father died recently, very traumatic, they were close.
Then can I suggest that she takes some time out and sorts herself out.
Because at this moment she's clearly not up to it.
Tanya?
There's nothing clever about overdoing it.
Vinny Haslam's first commandment - know your limitations.
Anybody fancy a Chinky?
Wing Yip do an Earlybird Special.
My treat.
Nita, I don't know what...
I think you should just go.
You watch.
This'll all be my fault.
He's probably right.
I have been overdoing it.
I tell you, guys, when you start hallucinating, you know you're in trouble!
I'll be fine in the morning.
I doubt it.
Thanks for the support!
I just don't think it's all gonna go away.
Oh?
And why's that?
Cos I saw him too.
Yeah, yeah.
I did.
I saw Dad.
Dan?
I need to tell you something.
'Hello, you've reached Phil Tyler's phone.
'Please leave your name and number after the beep.'
BEEP!
Phil?
I've come to a decision about the house.
Call me.
Nita, it's Dennis.
Is this a social call?
Not really.
Dennis and I have some business to discuss.
Well, that's weird.
Dennis asked me to come round at nine.
Well, don't just stand there!
Smile!
We're on camera!
Another Oscar-winning performance?
Look, I can come back later.
Oh, that'd be great actually.
No need!
What I have to say will interest you both.
As you know, I've had several offers for the house.
Yes.
Including, of course, from both of you.
What?
You didn't!
Which I've considered carefully, and finally come to a decision.
I've sold it.
To someone else.
What?
Yeah.
Made me a cracking good offer.
Well, you shouldn't sell yourself short, should you?
How much?
I'll better it.
No, I will!
Sorry.
I move out next week.
Dennis, you can't.
It's a done deal, I'm afraid.
And I think it's what Dad would've wanted.
New owners, fresh start.
They're gonna gut the place from top to bottom.
Ooh!
That'll be them now.
No, but I think Nita might.
What you said yesterday.
Desire.
'Are you feeling it?'
I might be.
'I didn't get you out of my system.'
Quite the reverse.
I don't want this to carry on.
It doesn't have to, Dennis, it doesn't have to.
I'm really really sorry.
She deserves to hear it face to face.
Where are you?
I'm with Phil.
Nita'll find out.
He'll have to choose, he'll choose you.
Family falls apart, Nita flips, business folds, we're on the streets.
Nita's out of control, Nita's as fallible as the rest of the human race.
I think you need help, Mum.
When were you going to tell me?
What?
About Mum?